MANUEL GONZALEZ

MANUELG139@GMAIL.COM | (469) 837 0618 | 5044 ROUNDTREE CT, FORT WORTH TX

OVERVIEW

Logistics, Sales, and Marketing specialist offering 6+ years of experience assisting companies in the North Texas area. In industries such as Finance, Real Estate, Technology, and Advertising. I've transcended all expectations and escalated the ladder at every professional opportunity using a unique style of analytics and creativity.

SKILLS

- Leadership
- Organization
- Project Management
- Event Coordinator
- Written& Oral Communication (English & Spanish)

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Adobe Creative CS6
- Salesforce.com
- LinkedIn Sales Navigator
- Zoominfo

REFERENCES

Anton Schlesinger (White Pants Agency)

-Anton@hiddenfriends.com (646) 706-2062

Matt Dennin (Restaurant 365)

MDennin@restaruant365.com (608) 70-0583

Jerry Aguirre (Wells Fargo)

-JerryA@wellsfargo.com

Lyndsey Kotrla (Realtorcom)

-lyndsey.kotrla@opcity.com (512) 694-0809

Skyler Littleaxe (Core Logic)

-SLittleaxe@corelogic.com (267) 342-2695

EXPERIENCE

Restaurant 365 (Austin, Tx) - Lead Development Specialist - Nov 2019 - March 2020

Prospecting and managing leads, accounts and opportunities in Salesforce. As an LDR, I was in charge of developing new leads for mid-market AEs using tools like Sales Navigator, ZoomInfo, Lusha, Seamless AI and more. As well as qualifying inbound inquiries via phone or web chat, working closely with AE's to better translate possible opportunities.

REALTOR.COM (Austin, Tx) - Consumer Success Representative - *March 2019 - Nov 2019*

Consumer coordinator pre-screening and connecting homebuyers with realtors and lenders in real-time. Turning daily Inbound and Outbound calls, texts and emails leads into potential warm introductions with clients.

White Pants Marketing Agency (Dallas, Tx) - 2yrs- Creative Content Director/ Event Coordiantor - May 2017 - March 2020

Managing creative direction and relations of branded content for social media as well as coordinating special promotional events for clients like Tidal, Off White, Moet, Monster Energy, Subway, Dr Pepper and more.

Wells Fargo (Denton, Tx) - Lead Teller - Feb 2012 - Sep 2015

Customer Service and sales as part of the Wells Fargo's teller team with the best regionals sales for 3 consecutive quarters in 2016

EDUCATION

TARRANT COUNTY COLLEGE (2009 - 2011) **FOSSIL RIDGE HIGH SCHOOL** (2005 - 2008)